myeduconnect.com 2011-11-23

# Privacy Policy - myEduConnect.com

Your Source for Educational Programs Nationwide

### Privacy Policy

My EDU Connect is owned and operated by Vast Interactive, LLC.

Vast Interactive knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. To make this Privacy Policy easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. By visiting Vast Interactive's primary Web site or related Web sites that Vast Interactive controls or operates (collectively “Vast Interactive Sites”), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Vast Interactive’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Vast Interactive gathers when you are accessing Vast Interactive Sites and when you use Vast Interactive services. Also, this Privacy Policy covers Vast Interactive’s treatment of any Personal Information that Vast Interactive’s business partners share with Vast Interactive. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the use of your Personal Information by third parties to which such information is provided by Vast Interactive that Vast Interactive does not own or control, or to individuals that Vast Interactive does not employ or manage.

#### What Personal Information Does Vast Interactive Collect And Maintain?

We collect the following types of information from our customers:

  * **Personal Information You Provide to Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on Vast Interactive Sites or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected may include name, address, phone number, and email address. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide is used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain products and services, customizing the advertising and content you see, and communicating with you about specials and new products.
  * **Personal Information Collected Automatically:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with Vast Interactive Sites or services. Vast Interactive automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 

Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to Vast Interactive Sites and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Vast Interactive uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Vast Interactive Sites or services so that we can make the Vast Interactive Sites appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers use Vast Interactive Sites. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use their services and Vast Interactive Sites, so that they, too, may seek to provide you with an optimal online experience. 

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit Web sites anonymously. While Vast Interactive will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

#### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in Vast Interactive Sites are visited and by how many people. Vast Interactive and its affiliated third parties may use cookies that collect Personal Information, and we may combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of Vast Interactive Sites’ most attractive features.

#### Will Vast Interactive Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We may share your Personal Information with the subsidiaries that are under control of Vast Interactive and as described below.

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:**  
We are affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses sell items or offer services to you through Vast Interactive Sites. In other situations, Vast Interactive provides services or sells products jointly with affiliated businesses, or helps to match affiliated businesses with prospective customers. You acknowledge that by disclosing Personal Information through an electronic form or similar means, you are making an inquiry or application regarding goods or services that may be provided by us or our business affiliates. We will only share Personal Information (i) with those affiliated businesses from which you have requested information, (ii) with affiliated businesses that matched your request for information or services submitted through an Vast Interactive Site, and (iii) only to the extent necessary to provide you with the information or services you requested; unless you have opted to receive offers from other affiliated businesses.
  * **Agents:**  
We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service.
  * **Business Transfers:**  
In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Vast Interactive, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or if Vast Interactive goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Vast Interactive may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. You hereby consent to Vast Interactive sharing your Personal Information under the above circumstances.
  * **Protection of Vast Interactive and Others:**  
We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Vast Interactive, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * **With Your Consent:**  
By visiting Vast Interactive Sites, or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

#### Is Personal Information About me Secure?

Vast Interactive is committed to online data security. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

#### What Personal Information Can I Access or correct?

You can correct factual errors in your Personal Information by sending a request to corrections at Vast Interactive that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take responsible steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to Personal Information.

#### What Choices Do I Have?

As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to us, even though it may be needed to take advantage of certain features on Vast Interactive Sites.

If you opt to disclose Personal Information to Vast Interactive through an Vast Interactive Site (whether by filling out an electronic form or otherwise), you acknowledge that Vast Interactive may disclose your Personal Information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

If you decide that you do not want Vast Interactive to disclose your Personal Information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, you may prevent such disclosure by sending email to optout at Vast Interactive.

If at any time you decide you no longer want to be contacted by Vast Interactive or its affiliated businesses, you may opt out by sending email to optout at Vast Interactive. To have your personal information completely removed from our databases you should send email to removeme at Vast Interactive. Please note that if you decide to opt out, you will not receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, but those legal notices will still govern your use of the Vast Interactive Sites, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

You are able to add or update certain information on pages, such as those listed in the “What Personal Information Can I Access or Correct” section above. When you update information, however, we often maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records.

As explained earlier, the majority of browsers allow you to monitor and restrict our use of cookies. Please note, however, that if you do not enable cookies, you will not be able to take advantage of some of our attractive features.

#### Our commitment to children’s privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at Vast Interactive Sites from those people we actually know are under 13 years old, and no part of any Vast Interactive Site is structured to attract anyone under 13 years old.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Vast Interactive may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes in the way we use Personal Information or otherwise materially change the terms of this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on Vast Interactive Sites.

#### Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at Vast Interactive Sites, please send us a detailed message to info@myeduconnect.com or to Attn: Privacy Officer, My EDU Connect, 650 Castro St, Ste 105, Mountain View, CA 94104, United States. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
